<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Hello on Jalingo</title>
    <link>http://www.jalingo.de/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Hello on Jalingo</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Jul 2020 12:00:50 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://www.jalingo.de/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Imprint</title>
      <link>http://www.jalingo.de/imprint/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 16:47:41 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jalingo.de/imprint/</guid>
      <description>Provider: Jalingo Management UG (limited liability)
Locarnoweg 6
12205 Berlin
Managing Director: Ingo Czok
Jurisdiction: Amtsgericht Berlin Charlottenburg
HRB 188860 B
Contact: Phone: + 49 30 54907246
e-mail: info@jalingo.de
Website: www.jalingo.de
For editorial content: Responsible according to ยง 55 Abs.2 RStV: Ingo Czok
Disclaimer Content of the online offer The Jalingo Management UG as the author of this website assumes no responsibility for the timeliness, Correctness, completeness or quality of the information provided.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Dataprotection</title>
      <link>http://www.jalingo.de/dataprotection/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 16:47:26 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jalingo.de/dataprotection/</guid>
      <description>General note and mandatory information Designation of the responsible body The person responsible for data processing on this website is
Jalingo Management UG (limited liability)
Ingo Czok
Locarnoweg 6
12205 Berlin
The responsible body decides alone or jointly with others on the purposes and means of processing personal data (e.g. names, contact details, etc.)
Revocation of your consent to data processing Only with your express consent are some data processing operations possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>http://www.jalingo.de/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 16:44:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jalingo.de/contact/</guid>
      <description>Please contact us through the following form for a swift reply. Thank you.
Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://www.jalingo.de/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jul 2020 10:13:19 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://www.jalingo.de/about/</guid>
      <description>Jalingo is an association of passionate individuals bringing technology to people Founded in 2017 Jalingo researches Blockchain, AI, and Mobile Technologies to identify their potential and use-cases for future software and services. Jalingo invests into companies that have a compelling business case utilizing those technologies.
Jalingo was founded by Ingo Czok who has co-founded Tembit (now Serrala) a leader in cloud and mobile solutions for corporate payments and corporate banking portals.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>